Suraj Jadhav

Software Engineer

Interested in the role of a Software Engineer where I can contribute my analytical skills and knowledge acquired by my 3+ years of experience in Software Engineering, Looking for a dynamic company where my skills are utilized in the maximum way possible.

iadhavsuraj777@gmail.com

+91 8407900055

www.hackerrank.com/jSuraj777

github.com/SurajJadhav7

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jr. Software Engineer Sephora SEA

09/2021 - Present

- Developed and maintained Sephora's 18 South Asian Country Websites working with established Agile Workflows and processes.
- As part of the NFM Squad, Fixed various reported issues and new enhancements in VueJS frontend and Ruby on Rails Backend.
- As part of Purchase Intent Squad, Fixed various issues in web application process from Add to Cart to Checkout functionality.
- Contributed to the fulfillment of technical projects functioning as an effective team member on multi-disciplinary teams.

System Engineer

Infosys (Clients: Apple, CVS Health)

08/2019 - 08/2021

- Developed a scripting tool which helps reduce the end to end transaction time by 90% using Shell script.
- Handled DevOps Migration process of previous shell scripts and C++ codes to the new systems as per the changed requirements.
- Currently working in QA team with Python, Robot Framework and Selenium on Apple's Internal Data Science and Analytics tool.

Systems Engineer Trainee Infosys

03/2019 - 07/2019 Mysore, India

- Completed 5 months training Program with the score of 89/100 and 92%le. Training involved Python, SQL and Mainframe Technologies.
- Developed a shopping application during the training using Mainframe technologies. Developed the cart module and integrated overall app.

PROJECTS

Hiddden Shelf

- Anyone can publish a blogpost on this simple website without any hassle. To post a blog on website, simply go to /compose url and post.
- Tech Stack: Node.js, MongoDB, Heroku, HTML, CSS and Javascript.
- Check it out at https://hidden-shelf-40003.herokuapp.com/.

Morning Headland

- Image Search Engine for any general english keyword like Nature, Books etc.
- Tech Stack: Node.js, Pexels API, Heroku on back-end and HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript on front-end.
- Check it out at https://morning-headland-75220.herokuapp.com/.

Other Projects

checkout my other projects on my github profile- https://github.com/SurajJadhav7

SKILLS



CERTIFICATES

Javascript Algorithms and Data Structures

https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/suraj055/jav ascript-algorithms-and-data-structures

Responsive Web Design Certification

https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/suraj055/res ponsive-web-design

Python Advanced Certification (Hackerrank)

https://www.hackerrank.com/certificates/b839041c0e78

Problem Solving Certification (Hackerrank)

https://www.hackerrank.com/certificates/a1bc725e68f4

Infosys Global Agile Developer Certification

Internal Infosys Certification

Javascript Certification

https://www.hackerrank.com/certificates/c6584af3dd0a

Web Developer Bootcamp

https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-a83b14f3-c74f-43cf-9ec4-16b702ea403b/

EDUCATION

B. Tech. (8.21/10)

Civil Engg, R.I.T. Sangli, Maharashtra

Class XII (88.6%), Class X (9.8/10)

Jawahar Navodaya Vidyalaya, Satara

HOBBIES

